This is a hot spot, [your favorite dish like a hot pot]
[You taste it once and] fall in love, [and now you can't go back]
[My girls] in the kitchen, cookin' it up, what you're craving?
[I flick my wrist, yeah, I'm] saucin' and now the world's gone mad
You don't need to think too much
[Oh, just savor all the flavor dancing on your tounge]
(Yeah, yeah, yeah!)
[Now my name is melting] in your mouth
Guilty pleasure never killed nobody, [try me out]
[I serve looks like] spaghetti, [I serve looks like] Bon appétit!
[All my girls hot and ready,] eat it up, eat it, eat it up!
[I serve looks like spaghetti,] bad dish in between your teeth
Eat it up, eat it, eat it (Whoa.)
Eat it up, eat it up! (Hey!)
Eat it up, eat it, eat it
Eat it up, eat it, eat it up!
Yeah, this is the sweet spot
Heat up the scene, it's that big shot
Chef's choice, [a kick specially for you]
You lost in the sauce? No turnin' back
[Gonna get tipsy all night, knock it back,]
[I'll take that empty glass, send back the useless sass]
[I like what I like, Do I need a reason, huh?]
[Get into it, every last drop, down the hatch]
Snap it up, like a Getty
[My kimchi pose is endlessly] priceless
Whatever I'm cookin', [I'm like a] star
[I'll cook any course you want]
[I'm the main character in your kind of drama,]
[Your guilty pleasure, your high-calorie] Hershy [chocolate]
[A tarot that shakes you, the flavor you savor]
[Ok now, from hater to believer,] brr!
Yeah, this is a hot spot, don't give a fork ['bout what you want]
[The minute that I hit your taste buds, I'm getting all] three star[s]
[You act like you] hate it, [so why did you cheat on your] diet?
[You sneak a bite when I can't see,] you better stop lying
Don't care what you talk about
[You keep coming back for seconds when you hear this sound]
(Yeah, yeah, yeah!)
[Now my name is melting] in your mouth
[Chew it over til you know what you can't live without]
[I serve looks like] spaghetti, [I serve looks like] Bon appétit!
[All my girls hot and ready,] eat it up, eat it, eat it up!
[I serve looks like spaghetti,] bad dish in between your teeth
Eat it up, eat it, eat it (Woah.)
Eat it up, eat it up! (Hey!)
Eat it up, eat it, eat it (Whoa.)
Eat it up, eat it, eat it up!
Eat it up, eat it, eat it up! (Hey!)
Eat it up, eat it, eat it (Whoa.)
Eat it up, eat it, eat it up!